A Guide to the Papers of Stanley Clay Walker
Special Collections and University Archives, J. Douglas and Patricia W. Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
The Papers of Stanley Clay Walker 1950 to 2000
Special Collections and University Archives, J. Douglas and Patricia W. Perry Library, Old Dominion University
28;
80 document cases
Served in the Virginia House of Delegates from 1964 to 1971, and has been a State Senator since 1972. Papers chiefly relate to his service in the General Assembly, notably his service as Chairman of the State Crime Commission.
Micheal J. Stolee
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Stanley Clay Walker, April 8, 1978 and Gift of Sybil Moore Walker September 12, 2005.
Biographical Information
Stanley Clay Walker was born July 2, 1923, in Norfolk, Virginia. He attended public schools in Norfolk and graduated from Fork Union Military Academy and the Norfolk Business College. When World War II began he enlisted in the United States Army and served in the European Theater, as part of an ordnance unit of the 82nd Airborne Division.
Following his discharge from service, Walker returned to Norfolk and became a partner in a steel fabricating and engineering firm. He married Sybil Bruce Moore, and had two daughters: Susan Gray Walker Meslang, who is one of the founders of the CHANCE educational program for disabled adults at Old Dominion University and Elizabeth Tray Walker, who is currently an attorney and government relations lobbyist for based in Alexandria, Virginia. Mrs. Walker served on the Board of Visitors, Old Dominion University, from March 30, 1990 to June 30, 1994. Walker served as President of Stanley Walker Associates, Inc. Walker was resided in Norfolk, until his death in 2001.
Walker, a Democrat, began his career in public service as a member of the Norfolk City School Board in 1959. This was shortly after the public schools reopened following the "Massive Resistance" program, which tried to thwart desegregation. Throughout his political career, Walker was a strong advocate for education on all levels. For his support of Old Dominion University throughout the years, when the school was transitioning from a college to a university, the Board of Visitors at the college awarded Walker as a resolution of appreciation, on September 17, 1992. The technology building at the Norfolk Campus of Tidewater Community College is named after him.
As one who wanted to reform the Democratic Party, he became active in a group known as "The Young Turks." Walker was elected to a seat in the House of Delegates in 1964 as a Representative of the consolidated 5th, 6th, and 7th districts of Norfolk. He took the oath of office on January 8, 1964, and served four terms there to 1971. In 1971, the Federal Court combined the senatorial districts into one multimember district and Walker took the oath of office as Senator on January 12, 1972. He served from that date until January 2000, representing parts of Norfolk and parts of Virginia Beach in the Sixth Senatorial District (Walker lost his bid for reelection in 1999). One aspect of Walker's distinguished career was his service on the Virginia State Crime Commission. He became its first chairman in 1966 and served in that position to 1979. He was also a strong advocate for the protection of children, in which he was chairman for the Commission on Early Childhood and Child Day Care Programs.
Stanley C. Walker passed away on January 15, 2001.
Walker's office listed his Senate positions as follows:
- President Pro Tempore: Elected by the Senate in 1988. Only member from Hampton Roads to ever hold this position. Responsibilities include assuming the duties of Lt. Governor in cases of vacancy, disability, or absence; procedural matters of the Senate; appointments to regional and national commissions; member of leadership team that confers with the Governor on matters of state.
- Standing Committees: Finance, Co-Chairman, and Chairman of the Finance Subcommittee on Education; Education and Health, former Chairman; General Laws, former Chairman; Rules Committee, former Chairman; Privileges and Elections, Joint Rules; Co-Chairman of the Joint Budget Conference Committee made up of four members each from the House and Senate. Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates.
- Legislative Commissions and Joint Committees: Joint Commission on Health Care, Chairman; Joint Legislative Audit and Review, former Chairman; Early Childhood and Child Day Care, Chairman; Equity in Public Education, Chairman; Small Business, Chairman; Reorganization of the Virginia State Library and Archives, Chairman; Future of Transportation in Virginia; State Water; Virginia Housing Study; State and Local Government Responsibility and Taxing Authority; Federal Block Grants; Educational Excellence; Educational Infrastructure; Future of Public Education; Preservation of the Capitol; Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation; State Law Enforcement Planning Council; Virginia State Crime Commission; Commission on Early Childhood and Child Day Care Programs.
-Civic organizations and boards: Norfolk Cosmopolitan Club; Planning Council of Hampton Roads; Isaac Walton League; Kempsville Ruritan; AF and AM; Corinthian Lodge No. 266; Norfolk City Recreation Commission; Norfolk Executives Club; Norfolk Citizen's Advisory Committee; First Virginia Bank of Tidewater; Leigh Memorial Hospital; Salvation Army State Advisory Board; Tidewater Association of Mental Health; Medical Center Hospital; Tidewater Toastmasters' Club.
Other Commissions (Boards, State, Regional, National) include: Senate Presidents' Forum, Board of Directors; Southern Legislative Conference (SLC) Executive Committee; SLC Education Committee, former Chairman; SLC Fiscal Affairs and Government Operations Committee, former Chairman; Eastern Regional Conference; National Conference of State Legislators (NCSL) Federal Budget and Taxation Committee; NCSL Legislative Management Committee; Southern Regional Education Board; National Leadership Conference; Council of State Governments Intergovernmental Affairs; Southern Growth Policies Board; Elizabeth River Project Leadership Review Board; Governor's Conference on Education; Jobs for Virginia Graduates, Board of Directors; Planning Council; Sentara Hospitals, Trustee Emeritus; Old Dominion Research Foundation Board.
Scope and Content
The Walker Papers consist of 35 linear shelf feet in 80 document cases. They deal primarily with his legislative duties as a member of the House of Delegates, 1964-1971 and his service as a member of the Senate from 1972 to 1977, serving parts of Norfolk and parts of Virginia Beach in the Sixth Senatorial District. The papers consist of personal and legislative correspondence, legislative papers and files, speeches, copies of bills introduced, news releases, statistical data, clippings, maps, a poster, and studies.
The first series in the collection is Correspondence (19 cases), which a substantial portion deals with legislative matters. The bulk of the collection can be found within in Series II: Legislative Papers (22 cases), pertaining to Walker's work within in the General Assembly, in which he dealt with issues such as education, bills and legislation, special sessions, transportation, Equal Rights Amendment, the establishment of the Eastern Virginia Medical School, as well as taxes and budgets. Series III: Legislative Files (10 cases), consists of loose books and binders of compiled materials that Walker kept in regard to issues within the General Assembly and his Senate campaigns. Series IV: Virginia State Crime Commission (13 cases), also makes up a significant part of the collection, in regard to Walker's work within the commission, which consists of statistics and data, conferences, prison visits, pari-mutuel betting and gambling, as well as information regarding sex crimes, juvenile crime, drug and alcohol abuse. Within Series V (5 cases), there are political files in regard to Walker's campaigns, as well as speeches he made for these campaigns, which are found in Series VI (2 cases).
Walker was very meticulous in collecting articles and clippings on issues within the state of Virginia, as well as personal interest. These clippings can be found in Series VI: Clippings (2 case) and VIII: Scrapbooks (4 cases). The scrap-books had to be scanned and copied, due to their fragile condition. There is also one case of miscellaneous materials (Series IX: Miscellaneous) which rounds out the collection.
Contents List
- Correspondence 1960s to 1990s
  Consists of correspondence both personal and legislative.
  chronological-alpha order
  - Personal Correspondence 1965 to 1996
    Pertains to the personal correspondence of Stanley C. Walker. Consists of personal letters, cards, children’s letters, as well as condolences.
    - Correspondence November 1965-September 1966 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Correspondence October-December 1966 (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Correspondence January-August 1967 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Correspondence September-November 1967, August-November 1968 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Correspondence 1972 (Box-folder 1:6)
    - Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Correspondence 1986 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Correspondence 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Correspondence 1990, 1992, 1993, 1995, 1996, 1999 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Children’s Letters 1972-1973 (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Condolences 1971-1974 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Condolences 1975-1977 (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Condolences 1996 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Legislative Correspondence 1960s to 1990s
    Legislative Correspondence. Pertains to the correspondence of when Walker was both a member of the House and Senate of the General Assembly of Virginia.
    chronological
    - Correspondence 1965-1967 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Correspondence February-March, 1968 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Correspondence March-December, 1968 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Correspondence January 1971 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Correspondence February 1971 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Correspondence March 1971 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Correspondence April 1971 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Correspondence May 1971 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Correspondence June 1971 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Correspondence July 1971 (Box-folder 3:11)
    - Correspondence August 1971 (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Correspondence September 1971 (Box-folder 3:13)
    - Correspondence October 1-5, 1971 (Box-folder 4:1)
    - Correspondence October 6-8, 1971 (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Correspondence October 12-15, 1971 (Box-folder 4:3)
    - Correspondence October 18-28, 1971 (Box-folder 4:4)
    - Correspondence November 3-29, 1971 (Box-folder 4:5)
    - Correspondence December 1-2, 1971 (Box-folder 4:6)
    - Correspondence December 6-8, 1971 (Box-folder 4:7)
    - Correspondence December 9-22, 1971 (Box-folder 4:8)
    - Correspondence December 27-31, 1971 (Box-folder 4:9)
    - Correspondence January 3-11, 1972 (Box-folder 4:10)
    - Correspondence January 11-20, 1972 (Box-folder 4:11)
    - Correspondence January 20-31, 1972 (Box-folder 4:12)
    - Correspondence February 1-5, 1972 (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Correspondence February 7-12, 1972 (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Correspondence February 12-19, 1972 (Box-folder 5:3)
    - Correspondence February 21-29, 1972 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Correspondence March 2-15, 1972 (Box-folder 5:5)
    - Correspondence March 16-31, 1972 (Box-folder 5:6)
    - Correspondence April 3-10, 1972 (Box-folder 5:7)
    - Correspondence April 11-14, 1972 (Box-folder 5:8)
    - Correspondence April 17-21, 1972 (Box-folder 5:9)
    - Correspondence April 25-28, 1972 (Box-folder 5:10)
    - Correspondence May 2-18, 1972 (Box-folder 5:11)
    - Correspondence May 19-31, 1972 (Box-folder 5:12)
    - Correspondence June 1-30, 1972 (Box-folder 5:13)
    - Correspondence July 3-31, 1972 (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Correspondence August 1-31, 1972 (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Correspondence September 1-26, 1972 (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Correspondence October 2-30, 1972 (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Correspondence November 1-30, 1972 (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Correspondence December 1-29, 1972 (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Correspondence January 2-6, 1973 (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Correspondence January 8-15, 1973 (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Correspondence January 16-24, 1973 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Correspondence January 25-31, 1973 (Box-folder 6:10)
    - Correspondence February 1-9, 1973 (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Correspondence February 10-28, 1973 (Box-folder 7:1)
    - Correspondence March 1-16, 1973 (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Correspondence March 19-30, 1973 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Correspondence April 2-30, 1973 (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Correspondence May 1-31, 1973 (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Correspondence June 1-29, 1973 (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Correspondence July 3-31, 1973 (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Correspondence August 1-31, 1973 (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Correspondence September 4-28, 1973 (Box-folder 7:9)
    - Correspondence October 1-31, 1973 (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Correspondence November 1-12, 1973 (Box-folder 8:2)
    - Correspondence November 13-30, 1973 (Box-folder 8:3)
    - Correspondence December 3-31, 1973 (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Correspondence January 2-11, 1974 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Correspondence January 14-16, 1974 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Correspondence January 17-22, 1974 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Correspondence January 23-25, 1974 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Correspondence January 26-28, 1974 (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Correspondence January 29-31, 1974 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Correspondence February 1-5, 1974 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Correspondence February 6-9, 1974 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Correspondence February 12-13, 1974 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Correspondence February 13, 1974 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Correspondence February 14-19, 1974 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Correspondence February 19-20, 1974 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Correspondence February 20-22, 1974 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Correspondence February 23-15, 1974 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Correspondence February 26, 1974 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Correspondence February 27, 1974 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Correspondence February 27-28, 1974 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Correspondence February 28-29, 1974 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Return to Sender February-March, 1974 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Correspondence March 1-5, 1974 (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Correspondence March 6-9, 1974 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Correspondence March 11-15, 1974 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Correspondence March 18-30, 1974 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - Correspondence April 1-15, 1974 (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Correspondence April 16-23, 1974 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Correspondence April 24-30, 1974 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Correspondence May 1-8, 1974 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Correspondence May 9-31, 1974 (Box-folder 11:11)
    - Correspondence June 3-7, 1974 (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Correspondence June 10-13, 1974 (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Correspondence June 14-19, 1974 (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Correspondence June 20-28, 1974 (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Correspondence July 1-31, 1974 (Box-folder 12:3)
    - Correspondence August 1-26, 1974 (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Correspondence September 3-30, 1974 (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Correspondence October 1-31, 1974 (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Correspondence November 1-13, 1974 (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Correspondence November 14-29, 1974 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Correspondence December 2-31, 1974 (Box-folder 12:9)
    - Correspondence January 3-13, 1975 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Correspondence January 14-22, 1975 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Correspondence January 22-25, 1975 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Correspondence January 27-31, 1975 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Correspondence February 3-14, 1975 (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Correspondence February 17-31, 1975 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Correspondence March 3-14, 1975 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Correspondence April 1-30, 1975 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Correspondence May 1-30, 1975 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Correspondence June 2-30, 1975 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Correspondence July 1-31, 1975 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Correspondence August 1-21, 1975 (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Correspondence September 2-30, 1975 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Correspondence October 2-28, 1975 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - Correspondence November 6-26, 1975 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - Correspondence December 1-30, 1975 (Box 15:4)
    - Correspondence January 2-20, 1976 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - Correspondence January 21-30, 1976 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - Correspondence February 1-10, 1976 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - Correspondence February 11-19, 1976 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Correspondence February 20-27, 1976 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Correspondence March 1-13, 1976 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Correspondence April 1-30, 1976 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Correspondence March 16-30, 1976 (Box-folder 16:5)
    - Correspondence May 3-27, 1976 (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Correspondence June 1-30, 1976 (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Correspondence July 1-28, 1976 (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Correspondence August 2-31, 1976 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Correspondence September 1-29, 1976 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Correspondence October 1-29, 1976 (Box-folder 17:3)
    - Correspondence November 1-30, 1976 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Correspondence December 1-29, 1976 (Box-folder 17:5)
    - Correspondence January-March 1977 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Correspondence March-August 1977 (Box-folder 17:7)
    - Correspondence 1986 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Correspondence 1987 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Correspondence 1988 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Correspondence 1989 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - Correspondence 1990-1991 (Box-folder 18:5)
    - Correspondence 1992 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1993 (Box-folder 18:7)
    - Correspondence February-December, 1993 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - Correspondence 1994 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - Correspondence 1995 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - Correspondence January-March, 1996 (Box-folder 18:11)
    - Correspondence April-May, 1996 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - Correspondence June-December, 1996 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 19:3)
    - Correspondence 1998 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Correspondence 1999 (Box-folder 19:5)
- Legislative Papers 1960s to 1990s
  Consists of papers relating to issues that Walker dealt with as both a member of the House and Senate of the General Assembly of Virginia.
  chronological-alpha
  - Committees 1968-1977
    Pertains to committees that Walker was a member of, or dealt with.
    alphabetical
    - Advisory Committee on Legislative Security 1975 (Box-folder 20:1)
    - Budget Advisory Committee 1975 (Box-folder 20:2)
    - Bush Organization/State Corporation Commission 1973 (Box-folder 20:3)
    - Commission of the Arts and Humanities 1972-1977 (Box-folder 20:4)
    - Commission on the Legislative Process 1969 (Box-folder 20:5)
    - Commission on Needs of Elderly Virginians 1975 (Box-folder 20:6)
    - Conflict of Interest Sub-Committee 1975 (Box-folder 20:7)
    - Folder 8: Courts of Justice Committee undated (Box-folder 20:8)
    - W. Fred Duckworth/Mac Arthur Memorial Foundation 1972 (Box-folder 20:9)
    - Economic Opportunity Programs undated (Box-folder 20:10)
    - Elections, State Board of 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20:11)
    - Governor’s Advisory Board on Budget 1971 (Box-folder 20:12)
    - House Committee Dockets 1968 (Box-folder 20:13)
    - Jamestown Foundation I undated (Box-folder 20:14)
    - Jamestown Foundation II undated (Box-folder 20:15)
    - Local and Area Organizations 1973, 1976 (Box-folder 20:16)
    - National Legislative Services and Security Association of the National Conference of State Legislatures-Advisory Committee undated (Box-folder 20:17)
    - Salvation Army I undated (Box-folder 20:18)
    - Salvation Army II undated (Box-folder 20:19)
    - Salvation Army III undated (Box-folder 20:20)
    - Salvation Army IV undated (Box-folder 21:1)
    - State Corporation Commission 1972-1974 (Box-folder 21:2)
    - Tidewater Consumer Council 1976 (Box-folder 21:3)
    - Urban Caucus 1971-1973 (Box-folder 21:4)
    - Virginia Council on State Legislation undated (Box-folder 21:5)
    - Young Democrats of Virginia-Advisory Committee 1974 (Box-folder 21:6)
  - Community 1971 to 1977, 1992
    Pertains to community issues that Walker had interest and concerns for.
    - Black Community 1973-1976 (Box-folder 21:7)
    - City of Norfolk undated (Box-folder 21:8)
    - Jewish Community 1971-1977 (Box-folder 21:9)
    - League of Women Voters 1973-1976 (Box-folder 21:10)
    - Local & Area Organizations: A-R 1973-1976 (Box-folder 21:11)
    - Media undated (Box-folder 21:12)
    - Norfolk Chamber of Commerce 1973-1977 (Box-folder 21:13)
    - Scottish Society of Tidewater 1975-1976 (Box-folder 21:14)
    - U.S. Navy-Tidewater Area 1973-1976, 1992 (Box-folder 21:15)
    - Virginia Beach (City of) undated (Box-folder 21:16)
  - Education 1964-1992
    Includes legislation and issues with public and higher education, as well as Walker’s recommendations and references for future college students.
    - Folder 17: Accreditation & Standards of Quality I undated (Box-folder 21:17)
    - Accreditation & Standards of Quality II undated (Box-folder 21:18)
    - Accreditation & Standards of Quality III undated (Box-folder 21:19)
    - Accreditation & Standards of Quality IV undated (Box-folder 22:1)
    - Accreditation & Standards of Quality V undated (Box-folder 22:2)
    - Adult/Vocational Education undated (Box-folder 22:3)
    - American Association of University Women 1973-1974 (Box-folder 22:4)
    - Appalachia Educational Laboratory 1970 (Box-folder 22:5)
    - Challenge to Lay Control Education-Speech undated (Box-folder 22:6)
    - Christopher Newport College undated (Box-folder 22:7)
    - Clinch Valley College undated (Box-folder 22:8)
    - Constitution of Virginia, Comments on 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22:9)
    - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia undated (Box-folder 22:10)
    - Description of Bills Relating to Education undated (Box-folder 22:11)
    - Educational Appropriations undated (Box-folder 22:12)
    - Education Commission of the States undated (Box-folder 22:13)
    - Education Committees: Virginia undated (Box-folder 22:14)
    - Education Legislation 1968-1971, 1976 (Box-folder 22:15)
    - Educational Practices Act-SB 560 I undated (Box-folder 22:16)
    - Educational Practices Act-SB 560 II undated (Box-folder 22:17)
    - Educational Practices Commission undated (Box-folder 23:1)
    - Financing of Public Schools Study SJR 29 1972 (Box-folder 23:2)
    - Governor’s Regional Conference on Education I 1966 (Box-folder 23:3)
    - Governor’s Regional Conference on Education II 1966 (Box-folder 23:4)
    - Governor’s Regional Conference on Education I 1967 (Box-folder 23:5)
    - Governor’s Regional Conference on Education II 1967 (Box-folder 23:6)
    - Governor’s Regional Conference on Education III 1967 (Box-folder 23:7)
    - House Appropriations Committee-Student Unrest Issue 1970 (Box-folder 23:8)
    - James Madison University undated (Box-folder 23:9)
    - Longwood College undated (Box-folder 23:10)
    - Mary Washington College undated (Box-folder 23:11)
    - Minority Issues and Educational Problems undated (Box-folder 23:12)
    - Norfolk Public Schools undated (Box-folder 23:13)
    - Norfolk State College undated (Box-folder 24:1)
    - Old Dominion College/University undated (Box-folder 24:2)
    - Radford College undated (Box 24:3)
    - Richmond Mercury, volume 3, number 7, Teacher’s Rationale for Collective Bargaining” October 23, 1974 (Box-folder 24:4)
    - SB-180 Professional Negotiations 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24:5)
    - School Health Nurses 1966 (Box-folder 24:6)